IHOR VOITIUK

Python Developer

CONTACTS

+31 630 210 297

GitHub

Hybrid, Remote, Office

ihorvoitiukk@gmail.com

<u>LinledIn</u>

• Dedeemsvaart, NL

SUMMARY

Motivated Python Developer with strong skills in both web development and data analysis. Specialized in web scraping, API development, and frontend/backend technologies. Passionate about programming, quick to learn, and an effective problem-solver. Demonstrated reliability and a proactive, goal-oriented approach, making me a valuable team player.

SKILLS

Languages: Python, JavaScript, SQL

Frontend: HTML, CSS/SCSS, Vue.js

Backend Frameworks: **Django**, **FastAPI / Node.js** (familiar)
Web Scraping: **Requests**, **AIOHTTP**, **Selenium**, **BeautifulSoup**

Data Analysis and Scientific Computing: NumPy, Pandas Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis

Testing: unittest, pytest / Postman

Version control: Git, GitHub, Bitbucket

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Python Developer at BLUE-BI SYSTEM

10/2023 - Present | Hoogeveen, Netherlands

Hybrid | Full-time

Developing software for productivity and efficiency

With expertise in both backend and frontend development, my duties involve designing, developing, and enhancing applications, debugging, and sometimes refactoring code to incorporate the latest technologies.

Technologies: Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Vue.js, AngularJS, Django, Django Rest Framework, FastApi, NumPy, MySQL, MongoDB, Bitbucket

Junior Python Developer at ADOREYES

07/2023 - Present | Canada

Remote | Part time

Cosmetic industry

I specialize in collecting and analyzing data from web pages to extract relevant information.

Technologies: Python, AIOHTTP, Requests, Selenium, BeautifulSoup, Pandas, MongoDB, Excel, GitHub

EDUCATION

Python Developer Master's degree in Finance, banking and insurance

Go IT Academy THE NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF WATER AND

2022-2023 | Kyiv, Ukraine ENVIRONMENTAL ENGINEERING

Focus: Python core | Python Web | Data Science 2016 - 2021 | Rivne, Ukraine

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian: Native Russian: Advanced (C1)

English: Intermediate (B1)

Dutch: Beginner